{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "By \u0027GoF Design Pattern\u0027 book, what are the 3 types/classifications of Design Patterns?",
      "answers": [
        "Construction,Interfaces,Operations",
        "Creational,Structural,Behavioral",
        "Construction,Structural,Behavioral"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "When the \u0027Mediator\u0027 Design Pattern is used?",
      "answers": [
        "When you need to ensure that only K instance of the object exists throughout runtime ",
        "When you have classes that can’t work together because of incompatible interfaces ",
        "When you want to reduce the complexity and dependencies between tightly coupled objects communicating directly with one another",
        "When you want to allow to create objects without specifying the exact class of object that will be created"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the goal of \u0027Validation testing\u0027 ?",
      "answers": [
        "To demonstrate to the developer and the system customer that the software meets its requirements",
        "To demonstrate to the developer and the system customer that the software conform to its specification",
        "To expose defects in the system "
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the definition of \u0027Unit testing\u0027 ?",
      "answers": [
        "The application system that provides the business services .",
        "The process that starts when you create an initial project plan during the project startup phase. ",
        "The process of testing individual components in isolation."
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "About 67% of the  total cost of a product accrues during the maintenance phase.",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Overall, which has the most maintenance effort distribution?",
      "answers": [
        "Environmental adaptation.",
        "Functionality addition or modification.",
        "Fault  repair."
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "MVC is composed of three components:",
      "answers": [
        "Model View Control",
        "Model View Controller",
        "Model Viewer Control",
        "Model Variable Control"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following can be considered regarding client and server?",
      "answers": [
        "Client and server is an architectural model",
        "Client and server can be architectural model",
        "Client and server is not an architectural model"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is not done in a review meeting ?",
      "answers": [
        "logging",
        "discussion",
        "fixing defects"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is right about code reviews ?",
      "answers": [
        "code reviews depends on the reviewer skills and motives",
        "code reviews dont fix anything",
        "code reviews require a big team",
        "code reviews fixes all of the defects"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not an example for non-functional requirements ?",
      "answers": [
        "System reliability",
        "System response time",
        "Storage requirement",
        "System behaviour"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What defines requirements validation ?",
      "answers": [
        "Make sure whether the developed product fulfills the requirements",
        "Figure out requirements conflicts",
        "Determine whether the requirements meet the customer’s needs",
        "Check if the requirement can ever be implemented by the given budget"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "Waterfall methodology can easily handle changes unlike Agile methodology",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should be done right after creating user stories ?",
      "answers": [
        "Design the product",
        "Prioritizing the user stories",
        "Start the development process",
        "Write tests"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "animal"
    }
  ]
}